FuKun Yun

Washington, DC

fukunyunqmty@gmail.com

949-806-9141

Summary

Mathematician and Physicist with four years of experience with data analysis for experimental data using python. Possess a deep understanding of mathematical logic, programming in python, and problem analysis, along with extraordinary perception for abstract mathematics and a keen sense for problem simplification.

Experience

Research Assistant

George Washington University

Jun 2023 - Dec 2023 (7 months)

Detected and predicted potential gene interactions using python.

Improved existing python-based algorithms independently to improve their accuracy in feature detection such as identifying and predicting potential interactions in a gene hic interaction map.

Independently developed a python algorithm to visually represent gene features different genes together in a single picture.

Research Assistant

University of California, Irvine

Sep 2021 - Feb 2022 (6 months)

Categorized data for Tokamak simulation data to improve future real Tokamak's performance and as well bring it one step closer to reality.

Improved existing Tokamak python algorithm to increase its ability to categorize different plasma patterns by 20%.

Incorporated knowledge from real analysis in math into python algorithms to identify the stability of each plasma simulation outcome.

Enhanced the efficiency for existing Tokamak python algorithms for them to process 10% faster.

Education

George Washington University

Master, Physics

University of California, Irvine

Bachelor, Mathematics and Physics Dean's List 2018-2019, 2021-2022

Skills

Python • Bash • SQL • R • Tableau • Quantitative/Qualitative Analysis • Microsoft Office • Data Analysis • Statistical Analysis • Data Modeling